[{"answer": "Fine, Piers.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Senator, how are you?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "You've been spitting blood all morning about Colin Powell endorsing Barack Obama again.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "I'm not angry about it.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Why are you so angry about it?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Of course not.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "Is that dignified for the president of the United States to use that term about his rival?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "I think it could be.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Could in the end Wisconsin potentially be more important than Ohio here?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Well, it will be interesting to see whether it holds or not, because, you know, there are many disparate groups in Syria now that are fighting against Bashar Assad ranging from jihadists which are pouring in to people who are pro-democracy so I'm not sure it holds.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- I think you have to look at this in its entirety.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "But without that original posting, then the e-mail at the center of your complaint becomes obsolete, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "I was.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Were you involved in all three of the president's debates this time?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Well, President Obama said that Governor Romney had a good night and he didn't, and I have to leave it at that.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "So what the hell happened on that first one?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "No, I don't go with that.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "You go along with that or not?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "What is your gut feeling about exactly where we are right now?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "There is no panic.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "Well, apparently Mr. Romney, Governor Romney, and his attorney are strangers to the truth not only with that comment but with many other comments they've made during this campaign, because, of course, I've not shopped them at all.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, we'll see what happens, obviously, with the legal action here.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "So I asked Governor Romney, how low can you stoop, Governor Romney, to allow your attorney to launch this attack on a single mom who you know cannot defend herself because she is still under that gag order?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Well, I wish I could say that it surprises me but it doesn't, because there is that kind of extremism in the Republican Party.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "Does this stagger you that these politicians running for the Senate, second one now, would say such extraordinary things about something as sensitive as rape and abortion and so on?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Well, I definitely support his right to have any religious conviction he wants.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Do you have a respect for people who perhaps don't phrase it such a clumsy way but have a religious conviction about the sanctity of life in any kind of situation like that?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I don't have a horse in the ring or dog in the fight because I'm Canadian.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "When you see the sexualization of the polling booth, as a woman, do you feel comfortable with that?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "No, that man has apologized.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "But what is more offensive, him doing that or him continuing to support a candidate for the Senate who thinks it's God's intent for women to be raped and impregnated?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "He hasn't apologized for what he said.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "But that -- do you think he's right?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Well, I think what this ad speaks to is the fact that 56 percent of voters are women and specifically in this independent swing vote that everybody is clamoring for, that is your demographic, that woman that created \"Girls.\"", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "But Marjorie Clifton, what do you think?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "I think there's another important thing.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "I'm doing your job for you, but what do you want to say to that?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Wait a minute.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Can we have a -- can we have the same conversation that America's women are having across the country?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Well, it is a problem on the flip-flopping.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Are you falling for it?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "I'm well.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "John, how are you?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "I was trying not to.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "Were you listening to those three feisty ladies going at it just now?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "Well, look, I think last time I was on your program, I said presidential campaigns are like basketball games.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "What is your reading of it all?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Yeah, no, I don't.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Would you accept that charge?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "And then you have somebody like Richard Mourdock, who wants to be a senator, coming out and saying basically it's God's intent when women are impregnated by rapists, you must groan, don't you?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "I'm not sure how important that is.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Is it time he left the party, do you think?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Well, I think when you have somebody of your own race that you are proud of being president of the United States, I applaud Colin for standing with him.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "What reason would that be?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "My dad always said there's only two things in the middle of the road.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Are you pleased to see your offspring being so active in this area?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "My view is that, you know, America's coming out of a deep hole.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "What is your view of where the country is?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "I'm going to vote for him again.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "You would vote for him again?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "I guess I am.", "docId": "121025pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Dedicating it to Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 571}]